<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WINNITRON</title>
    <description>An open source platform for indie
arcade machines and games.
</description>
    <link>http://winnitron.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://winnitron.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 23:34:36 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 23:34:36 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Winnitron Release v2-Beta1</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Heck yeah! Winnitron Network beta is open. If any of you would like to take the new launcher and website out for a spin (and hopefully give us some feedback), that would be awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go download the launcher from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/winnitron/WinnitronLauncher/releases&quot;&gt;GitHub releases page&lt;/a&gt;, there will be installation instructions on the wiki there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://network.winnitron.com&quot;&gt;Winnitron Network site&lt;/a&gt; and sign up, etc.  Don’t judge the design (i.e. lack thereof) too harshly quite yet; we’re mainly looking for bugs and what you think about general workflows etc right now.  Post any issues you have with the site on the relevant &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/winnitron/winnitron_reborn/issues&quot;&gt;GitHub issues page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Post feedback or questions on this post or on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/winnitron/comments/5frgkl/release_winnitron_v2beta1/&quot;&gt;Winnitron Reddit&lt;/a&gt; and submit any glaring issues on our &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/winnitron/WinnitronLauncher/issues&quot;&gt;GitHub issues page for the launcher&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note that everything is still very much a work in progress and we need your help to get it all working smoothly!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://winnitron.com/news/posts/test</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://winnitron.com/news/posts/test</guid>
        
        
        <category>release</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Winnitron Website</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey!  Welcome to the new Winnitron website.  We’re excited to show you some of the stuff we’ve been working on in the last couple months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Winnitron project is now &lt;a href=&quot;http://github.com/winnitron&quot;&gt;entirely on GitHub&lt;/a&gt;, if you’re web inclined you could help us with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/winnitron/winnitron.github.io&quot;&gt;design of this site&lt;/a&gt; or the &lt;a href=&quot;http://network.winnitron.com&quot;&gt;Winnitron Network&lt;/a&gt; where you can manage the games on your Winnitron easily.  If you have some Unity background, feel free to &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/winnitron/WinnitronLauncher&quot;&gt;fork the launcher&lt;/a&gt; and tackle some the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/winnitron/WinnitronLauncher/issues&quot;&gt;issues&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also just made a &lt;a href=&quot;http://reddit.com/r/winnitron&quot;&gt;Winnitron subreddit&lt;/a&gt; for more conversation, so if you have any questions comments or concerns, post ‘em on this post or over on the reddit.  We’re still trying to figure out the best way to stay in touch with Winnitron users, so let us know!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://winnitron.com/news/posts/new-website</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://winnitron.com/news/posts/new-website</guid>
        
        
        <category>release</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
